# Max Moses

E-Mail: mmoses99@gmail.com

Social: max.moses

Phone: +1(248) 535 5044

## Objective

Searching for employment or experience opportunities in the field of Experience Architecture.

#### **Skills**

<u>Leadership</u>: Being a part of multiple sports teams, work environments, and academic clubs has shaped my leadership qualities and ability to work well with others. I am highly capable of listening to instruction and never afraid of a leadership role.

<u>Communication</u>: Academics and athletics have taught me how important it is to communicate with others. I have learned that it is very difficult to succeed without constant and concise communication.

<u>Technology</u>: As a previous computer science major, I take great pride and interest in technology. I am to the best of my ability learning as much about the ever expanding field of technology.

Experience in: Python, C++, HTML, CSS.

<u>Creativity</u>: Through my time studying experience architecture, I have been exposed to various facets of design and creative development. With deep interest in graphic design, fashion, and the arts, I am always eager to take my knowledge and skill set to the next level.

Experience in: Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, XD.

## Experience

Kate Spade | Auburn Hills, MI

Sales Associate (Nov 2018 - Apr 2019)

Part-time sales associate working to assist customers in store while ensuring they enjoy their time shopping. Tasks often included locating products, operating the cash register, and unpacking/organizing stock shipment. This job required a lot patience and a great amount of communication skills to guarantee customer satisfaction.

Honcho Restaurant | Clarkston, MI Busser (Apr 2017 - Aug 2018)

Here I developed teamwork skills while working in a fast pace environment. Tasks included cleaning of interior and exterior of restaurant as well as providing assistance to servers and staff when needed. As a busser I was always on my toes, ready for anything that came my way.

### Education

Michigan State University (Aug 2017 - Present)

- Experience Architecture Major
- 3.0 GPA

Lake Orion High School (Sept 2013 – Jun 2018)

- National Honors Society
- Student Leadership Workshop
- Over 150 community service hours
- 3.75 GPA